<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://www.fazhion.xyz</id>
    <title>Fazhion</title>
    <updated>2021-11-14T03:07:43.895Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.fazhion.xyz"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://www.fazhion.xyz/atom.xml"/>
    <subtitle>Do Some Women&apos;s Fashion Thing!</subtitle>
    <logo>https://www.fazhion.xyz/images/avatar.png</logo>
    <icon>https://www.fazhion.xyz/favicon.ico</icon>
    <rights>All rights reserved 2021, Fazhion</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2021 Fall/Winter essential nail art!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.fazhion.xyz/post/2021-fallwinter-essential-nail-art/</id>
        <link href="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post/2021-fallwinter-essential-nail-art/">
        </link>
        <updated>2021-11-14T01:43:07.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>A woman's beauty is from head to toe, and many women will not let go of the beauty of any detail of their bodies. The hands are the most frequently used limbs in our daily life, and they are also one of the parts that women pay the most attention to. The prevalence of nail art has brought a new pursuit of beauty to every woman, that is, the fingers can be beautiful, which has become the symbol of the new era of women.<br>
What is the necessary nail art for this fall and winter? All of these nail art represents the popular fashion for the fall/winter season of 2021, so it is worth to talk or discuss about it specially. What kind of effect can these nail art give us, is it whitening or temperament? Whether it is the former or the latter, they are what women are constantly seeking. If you're interested, let's explore the trends for the fall and winter seasons!<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636854358451.png" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<h2 id="1persimmon-nail-art">1.Persimmon nail art</h2>
<p>As the name implies, it is a persimmon nail art, which uses persimmon as the base color for the nail art, and then uses other colors as secondary shades. The purpose of this color scheme is that persimmon is a very white base color that will make your fingers look white. This is a great way to make your hands look white and not monotonous, so it's a good idea for girls who are still in school or young to try it out.<br>
The subtlety of this nail art lies in the fact that if it had persimmon color as the main color for a large area, then this nail art would have become plain and boring. Instead, it goes the other way and chooses other light colors as secondary colors, and the whole temperament is different. The nail becomes clear and lively at the same time, which is the fashion trend for this fall and winter season.<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636854369427.png" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<h2 id="2-crystal-jelly-nail-art">2. Crystal jelly nail art</h2>
<p>The nail art is very easy to understand, it is the nail art that is shaped by the nail polish with various colors. This one is mainly in peach color with blue edge of the nail head to achieve a girly look for the fall and winter season. The blue border is lively and gentle, and the simple style is not monotonous and boring. It is suitable for girls who like simple style, but also for girls who want to take a temperament style.<br>
The clear crystal jelly also meets the temperament of the autumn and winter season, and the gentle temperament of a young girl comes through between the clear nail. The border carries a slight French temperament that is heartwarming and satisfies the basic requirement of showing white as a nail art.<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636854376526.png" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<h2 id="3-french-nail-art">3.  French nail art</h2>
<p>This black and green French nail art is slightly different from the normal French nail art, it has a cool style with a black and green tone. Many people think that French and cool are two styles, but they don't think that they can be combined. Black is the main color that gives the nail a white base, while fluorescent green brings a cool tech feel through fluorescence.<br>
This manicure is perfect for girls who go for a cool style, because the border also completes the basic French pattern. This manicure is also considered a French gentle rebellion. It completes an innovative nail art style with a cool vibe fused with French nail art!<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636854383527.png" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>The nail art above is actually white in tone, so the nail art style itself is very intentional. With white as the base tone, then the other auxiliary colors can play a wonderful effect, which makes them the trend of this year. In short, the blogger was moved, I wonder if we should also try it?</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced red leopard print nail art collection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.fazhion.xyz/post/advanced-red-leopard-print-nail-art-collection/</id>
        <link href="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post/advanced-red-leopard-print-nail-art-collection/">
        </link>
        <updated>2021-11-13T08:07:15.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Today the blogger is going to share with you a set of very distinctive red leopard print nail art. When it comes to leopard print nails, I believe you are no stranger to it. Leopard print nails with a unique fur texture are very popular in this autumn and winter. The various colors of leopard print nail are very characteristic, and today the blogger will have to show you this group of leopard print nail, but also the leopard print nail in a very classic color, do not miss!<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636790866556.png" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636790871683.png" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>Red solid color nail art is very simple and generous, even without any decoration, it will look extra popular. The fashionable qualities of leopard print nail art and red solid color nail art are very suitable, and these two styles are very suitable to combine.<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636790923025.png" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636790929757.png" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>Leopard nail art can also be made in many different effects, depending on the color combination of the leopard nail art. For example, a leopard print manicure created by combining red and black on a white nail surface looks very fresh and sexy at the same time, presenting a diverse charm that is perfect for girls with different personalities.<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636790966187.png" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636790971765.png" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>The frosted texture of leopard print nail art is also a style that many fashionistas like. The matte nail surface can better restore the fur texture of the leopard print, making the leopard print look more realistic, while also increasing the fashionable temperament of the nail, low-key and very gorgeous, fashionable and not flashy, very unique!<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636791003520.png" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636791008795.png" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>The leopard print nail created by combining beans and black will look showing the girly style. It is a very simple yet classy and charming nail art with a solid color of burgundy and bean paste. This color scheme will not look tacky at all, making the leopard print a fashion icon at the fingertips.<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636791046494.png" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>The combination of leopard print nail art and lace-up nail art is also a very popular style. The strap element is a common style in the fashion world, and combining it with leopard print to make a nail art will look extra chic and add a sense of sophistication to the fingertips without looking fancy, which is very beautiful.<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636791080370.png" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636791085579.png" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>Leopard print nails have a small texture and look relatively dense, so they are not suitable for a single style. If you do leopard nail art on all ten fingers, it will look fancy and have a dazzling feeling, so usually we choose a simple solid color nail with leopard nail art, which can neutralize the fancy feeling of leopard print and make the fingertips look more atmospheric.<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636791118554.png" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>The patchwork nail art created with leopard print and solid color looks simple and chic and will be more distinctive than the simple style.<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636791157129.png" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636791163815.png" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>For the sophisticated girl, you can also use leopard print nail art with some nude translucent texture luminous nail art. This will make the fingertips look shinier, like some nude translucent texture diamond nails, or nude translucent shell gold foil, nails, which will make the fingertips look more agile and look young. It's also great to mix and match with leopard print nail and red nail, which will make the whole nail look more layered!<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636791198776.png" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636791204175.png" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>Red leopard print nail art is perfect for girls with short nails. The simple red solid color nail art will make the fingertips look more slender by the light and shadow. The leopard print will look more delicate in a small area of the nail surface, and it looks simple and trendy with it, so that even short nail girls can keep up with the fashion trends.<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636791249856.png" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636791256378.png" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636791261434.png" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>Combining a red leopard print manicure on a silver sequin nail will be very unique. The signature texture of leopard print will look extra sophisticated with the glamorous glow of sequins. This unique pairing will also make the fingertips even more unique!<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636791307298.png" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636791313456.png" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636791318829.png" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>Red leopard print nail art and delicate whole nail diamond nail art together, so that the fingertips look exquisite and shiny charming, full of fashion temperament, really super beautiful.<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636791350053.png" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636791357086.png" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>Pairing a solid red manicure with a delicate leopard print manicure is a very refreshing look. Such a style would be perfect for busy working professionals. Not only will it not be a burden on your work and life, but it's very chic and brings out your workplace charm even more!<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636791403354.png" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636791408479.png" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>Red leopard print nail art is really beautiful, so don't miss it! If you like it, hurry up and collect it! Follow the blogger, there are different surprises every day!</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bridal Nail Art Styles Winter 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://www.fazhion.xyz/post/bridal-nail-art-styles-winter-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post/bridal-nail-art-styles-winter-2021/">
        </link>
        <updated>2021-11-13T06:42:50.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="1red-glitter-nail-art">1.Red Glitter Nail Art</h2>
<p>Look at this new nail 2021, very festive, especially for the bride's nail, red nail mixed with gold glitter, bling bling feeling very upscale, giving people a full sense of high tone, and especially show hands white, but also more atmospheric one. A look let people fascinated feeling, big red is very suitable for winter.<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636786068145.png" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<h2 id="2flower-pattern-nail-art">2.Flower Pattern Nail Art</h2>
<p>Very fresh and gentle nail style, the color is very understated. Plain color in the small flower pattern set off no longer look monotonous, simple and generous and vibrant sense, painted on the nail a layer of cream color, delicate and soft, fresh and sweet, temperament more outstanding, just meet you to change nail,  try this new winter 2021 nail！<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636786074038.png" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<h2 id="3leopard-print-frosted-nail-art">3.Leopard Print Frosted Nail Art</h2>
<p>The new nail in the winter of 2021, leopard elements with frosted style, sexy and warm, looks especially noble sensational. Leopard print, frosted between the jump color design, full of details, get rid of the conventional nail earthy tone! Once dyed, you can't help but love the frosted leopard girl, it's worth trying!<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636786079412.png" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<h2 id="4cats-eye-blue-manicure">4.Cat's Eye Blue Manicure</h2>
<p>The blue temperament, looks energetic and gentle, this winter's warm new cat eye, nail style, durable and white, really nice. Anyway, Jessica is moved, senior sense full of cat eye, nail plus glitter embellishment, with just the right amount of beauty, simply good to see a burst of nail, super like, feel photos can not reflect its beauty, or experience it in person.<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636786084717.png" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<h2 id="5green-nail-art">5.Green Nail Art</h2>
<p>Green gives a very clean feeling, this winter's new style. The winter atmosphere you can not miss ,  which is very light and contain green and polka dot nail combination, can be said to be very gentle wind. It's white and green, visually have a strong contrast visual impact, giving a very unique feeling, and the hands look very white. When the moment of swinging fingers, it shows the formation of a lively sense of activity!<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636786109040.png" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Top 5 Little Fresh Nail Art In Autumn]]></title>
        <id>https://www.fazhion.xyz/post/the-top-5-little-fresh-nail-art-in-autumn/</id>
        <link href="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post/the-top-5-little-fresh-nail-art-in-autumn/">
        </link>
        <updated>2021-11-12T12:40:50.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>​Hands are our second face of women, so many of our friends are very fond of doing nail art,  especially now in autumn,  do some beautiful,  white-looking style can make people feel good,  so what is the autumn little fresh nail art in the end?  What is the hottest?  Today,  I will bring you a detail introduction.</p>
<h2 id="1-shiny-gold-nail-art">1. Shiny Gold Nail Art</h2>
<p>​Although it has to be applied to real life,  these gorgeous and advanced nail styles are something that you can not help but try. Many peeps select elongated styles to bring out their high-end feel,  but for the convenience of life,  these shorts are also perfect. Use your favorite color as a base,  then apply shiny gold on top,  these somewhat monotonous appearance,  become instantly luxurious. For instance,  this pink nail art with the addition of shining gold looks very special.<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636720921249.png" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<h2 id="2-white-small-flower-nail-art">2. White Small Flower Nail Art</h2>
<p>​These solid color mirror nails are still loved by many young in real life. The so-called plain mirror color is a nail art that is chosen with a single color,   with no additional color added. Combined with the smooth appearance,  it looks shiny when exposed to light or sunlight.  Naturally there will be people who don't like this slightly monotonous nail art,  so adding a few small touches can be an effective solution to this problem.  This fishing manicure with the small white flower added on top is very soft and soft.<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636720933203.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<h2 id="3-white-edge-nail-art">3. White Edge Nail Art</h2>
<p>​If you don't want to add small white flowers,  you think the accents are a bit brusque. There are many other options at this point, after all, nail art can be whatever you want it to be,  and if you are handy enough,  you can totally design it for yourself.  The nail is painted with a colour and a white border is added at the top.  This style of nail art is quite popular amongst girls nowadays.  Not only does it add a vivid colour,  but it also looks very neat.<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636720939000.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>​The nail art above,  in its entirety,  is pink and then a white border is painted on top. The combination of soft pink and vivid white,  is unique and distinctive. This one has a blue border,  which is as pink overall,  but the color is lighter than the one above.  This nail art looks very cool and enjoyable after adding a blue border.  This way,  you can see that the colour of the ridge can be chosen at will.<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636720944290.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<h2 id="4-color-blocking-nail-art">4. Color Blocking Nail Art</h2>
<p>​Like the side nail art,  which is also made up of two colors,  the color blocking nail art is worth a try.  This nail art,  composed of blue and white,  is perfect for light autumn days and brings a touch of pleasure to the heart. This nail art is slightly different,  since it is only on the ring finger.  If you think it's a bit monotonous,  you can freely choose the color that you want to put together,  and it's not limited to one color.  In addition,  you can choose a color combination on each nail,  but this will look a bit tedious.<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636720953456.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<h2 id="5-color-jumping-nail-art">5. Color Jumping Nail Art</h2>
<p>​Last but not least,  I would like to share with you a color jumping manicure.  As the name suggests,  color jumping means that the nails are one color apart but different. The one I'm introducing is made up of green and white,  with white on the thumb,  middle finger and little finger,  and green on the index finger and ring finger.  The two colors set off each other and look very original and unique.<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636720960687.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Burgundy Nail Art Collection For Autumn 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://www.fazhion.xyz/post/burgundy-nail-art-collection-for-autumn-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post/burgundy-nail-art-collection-for-autumn-2021/">
        </link>
        <updated>2021-11-12T12:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>When fall arrives, it's time for a new manicurist! You need a nail form that can show the white, it's time for a wave of &quot;maroon&quot; nails. The nails of Burgundy are rich and magnificent, both magnificent and fresh, bringing a lasting and generous temperament.Here are a few &quot;burgundy&quot; nail art that will show off your white hands.<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636720683474.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>Recently, this chic, lightweight luxury nail is very popular, with the dark maroon color as the main color, super white, with diamond elements. The nail with his own sense of temper, both romantic and trendy, seems very excited about it?<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636720691881.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>The basic color of autumn nail is partial carrion color, with the snowflakes show beauty, with the elk like a little princess in Christmas. You can feel the lively atmosphere when you paint on your fingertips!<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636720696751.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>Who says that burgundy can not create small freshness, match with clear colors, and it can also be harnessed by young girls. Transparent colour and burgundy interval, dotted elements to bring a vintage freshness, for burgundy to bring a feeling of freshness. Bordeaux is very inclusive and is great for black and yellow hands.<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636720701716.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>In autumn, the matte matte makeup effect became popular, and the bright glitter of the makeup is different. Matte will seem more advanced, and the season corresponding to the full sense of cool, chic and beautiful!<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636720707568.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>In early autumn, our nail art can continue to continue the qualities of summer, like some lively colors, or some relatively clear shell jump colors, which are also still popular in early autumn.<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636720716241.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>It is the most popular color in the fashion world, and it exudes the charming atmosphere of red wine, which is both elegant and understated luxury, interpreting the femininity to the fullest. The actual nail art is a very good choice for the nail.<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636720721612.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>Red nails show very white skin tone, so they also give a cool look. The light in autumn will look dull, choose dark red and the milk tea color combination will focus the light to the nail of the girl's dress looks brighter. In addition to this halo style highlights rich and energetic girl's atmosphere.<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636720726252.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>Beige is also a very gentle color which is chosen with burgundy jump color show extraordinarily versatile. At the fingertips embellished with some diamonds, exquisite design seems to make nails look small, but not lose elegance, just like a genie in the air. Other fingertips as long as a little embellished with a little line are very good-looking.<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636720731238.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>The combination of small flower patterns and burgundy frosted nails together really look good. To be honest, it is very heartwarming for the nail at the first look. Not only show hands white and also super good-looking, the flower pattern are lifelike and exquisite. Such a color lining shows a small touch of freshness and makes people feel comfortable.<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636720736232.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>Pearl nail art has been a wave of trend for a while now, it can be as proud as a little princess, or as dignified as a queen, and as rosy as a little girl. Choosing a finger edge glued with a small pearl, it is really simple and durable! No matter which season it is, it can shine.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>