<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://www.fazhion.xyz</id>
    <title>Gridea</title>
    <updated>2021-11-12T12:52:04.962Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.fazhion.xyz"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://www.fazhion.xyz/atom.xml"/>
    <subtitle>温故而知新</subtitle>
    <logo>https://www.fazhion.xyz/images/avatar.png</logo>
    <icon>https://www.fazhion.xyz/favicon.ico</icon>
    <rights>All rights reserved 2021, Gridea</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Top 5 Little Fresh Nail Art In Autumn]]></title>
        <id>https://www.fazhion.xyz/post/the-top-5-little-fresh-nail-art-in-autumn/</id>
        <link href="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post/the-top-5-little-fresh-nail-art-in-autumn/">
        </link>
        <updated>2021-11-12T12:40:50.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>​Hands are our second face of women, so many of our friends are very fond of doing nail art,  especially now in autumn,  do some beautiful,  white-looking style can make people feel good,  so what is the autumn little fresh nail art in the end?  What is the hottest?  Today,  I will bring you a detail introduction.</p>
<h2 id="1-shiny-gold-nail-art">1. Shiny Gold Nail Art</h2>
<p>​Although it has to be applied to real life,  these gorgeous and advanced nail styles are something that you can not help but try. Many peeps select elongated styles to bring out their high-end feel,  but for the convenience of life,  these shorts are also perfect. Use your favorite color as a base,  then apply shiny gold on top,  these somewhat monotonous appearance,  become instantly luxurious. For instance,  this pink nail art with the addition of shining gold looks very special.<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636720921249.png" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<h2 id="2-white-small-flower-nail-art">2. White Small Flower Nail Art</h2>
<p>​These solid color mirror nails are still loved by many young in real life. The so-called plain mirror color is a nail art that is chosen with a single color,   with no additional color added. Combined with the smooth appearance,  it looks shiny when exposed to light or sunlight.  Naturally there will be people who don't like this slightly monotonous nail art,  so adding a few small touches can be an effective solution to this problem.  This fishing manicure with the small white flower added on top is very soft and soft.<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636720933203.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<h2 id="3-white-edge-nail-art">3. White Edge Nail Art</h2>
<p>​If you don't want to add small white flowers,  you think the accents are a bit brusque. There are many other options at this point, after all, nail art can be whatever you want it to be,  and if you are handy enough,  you can totally design it for yourself.  The nail is painted with a colour and a white border is added at the top.  This style of nail art is quite popular amongst girls nowadays.  Not only does it add a vivid colour,  but it also looks very neat.<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636720939000.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>​The nail art above,  in its entirety,  is pink and then a white border is painted on top. The combination of soft pink and vivid white,  is unique and distinctive. This one has a blue border,  which is as pink overall,  but the color is lighter than the one above.  This nail art looks very cool and enjoyable after adding a blue border.  This way,  you can see that the colour of the ridge can be chosen at will.<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636720944290.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<h2 id="4-color-blocking-nail-art">4. Color Blocking Nail Art</h2>
<p>​Like the side nail art,  which is also made up of two colors,  the color blocking nail art is worth a try.  This nail art,  composed of blue and white,  is perfect for light autumn days and brings a touch of pleasure to the heart. This nail art is slightly different,  since it is only on the ring finger.  If you think it's a bit monotonous,  you can freely choose the color that you want to put together,  and it's not limited to one color.  In addition,  you can choose a color combination on each nail,  but this will look a bit tedious.<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636720953456.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<h2 id="5-color-jumping-nail-art">5. Color Jumping Nail Art</h2>
<p>​Last but not least,  I would like to share with you a color jumping manicure.  As the name suggests,  color jumping means that the nails are one color apart but different. The one I'm introducing is made up of green and white,  with white on the thumb,  middle finger and little finger,  and green on the index finger and ring finger.  The two colors set off each other and look very original and unique.<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636720960687.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Burgundy Nail Art Collection For Autumn 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://www.fazhion.xyz/post/burgundy-nail-art-collection-for-autumn-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post/burgundy-nail-art-collection-for-autumn-2021/">
        </link>
        <updated>2021-11-12T12:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>When fall arrives, it's time for a new manicurist! You need a nail form that can show the white, it's time for a wave of &quot;maroon&quot; nails. The nails of Burgundy are rich and magnificent, both magnificent and fresh, bringing a lasting and generous temperament.Here are a few &quot;burgundy&quot; nail art that will show off your white hands.<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636720683474.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>Recently, this chic, lightweight luxury nail is very popular, with the dark maroon color as the main color, super white, with diamond elements. The nail with his own sense of temper, both romantic and trendy, seems very excited about it?<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636720691881.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>The basic color of autumn nail is partial carrion color, with the snowflakes show beauty, with the elk like a little princess in Christmas. You can feel the lively atmosphere when you paint on your fingertips!<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636720696751.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>Who says that burgundy can not create small freshness, match with clear colors, and it can also be harnessed by young girls. Transparent colour and burgundy interval, dotted elements to bring a vintage freshness, for burgundy to bring a feeling of freshness. Bordeaux is very inclusive and is great for black and yellow hands.<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636720701716.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>In autumn, the matte matte makeup effect became popular, and the bright glitter of the makeup is different. Matte will seem more advanced, and the season corresponding to the full sense of cool, chic and beautiful!<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636720707568.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>In early autumn, our nail art can continue to continue the qualities of summer, like some lively colors, or some relatively clear shell jump colors, which are also still popular in early autumn.<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636720716241.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>It is the most popular color in the fashion world, and it exudes the charming atmosphere of red wine, which is both elegant and understated luxury, interpreting the femininity to the fullest. The actual nail art is a very good choice for the nail.<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636720721612.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>Red nails show very white skin tone, so they also give a cool look. The light in autumn will look dull, choose dark red and the milk tea color combination will focus the light to the nail of the girl's dress looks brighter. In addition to this halo style highlights rich and energetic girl's atmosphere.<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636720726252.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>Beige is also a very gentle color which is chosen with burgundy jump color show extraordinarily versatile. At the fingertips embellished with some diamonds, exquisite design seems to make nails look small, but not lose elegance, just like a genie in the air. Other fingertips as long as a little embellished with a little line are very good-looking.<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636720731238.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>The combination of small flower patterns and burgundy frosted nails together really look good. To be honest, it is very heartwarming for the nail at the first look. Not only show hands white and also super good-looking, the flower pattern are lifelike and exquisite. Such a color lining shows a small touch of freshness and makes people feel comfortable.<br>
<img src="https://www.fazhion.xyz/post-images/1636720736232.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>Pearl nail art has been a wave of trend for a while now, it can be as proud as a little princess, or as dignified as a queen, and as rosy as a little girl. Choosing a finger edge glued with a small pearl, it is really simple and durable! No matter which season it is, it can shine.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>